

# Sadat Asif Ahmed

## **SKILLS**

I can work in Microsoft Office, Google DOCS, etc. I have basic skills in Web Development, I am skilled in Photography, and can edit videos. I have been tutoring for more than 3 years. Previously I used to teach at a coaching center. I was part of a team which hosted a lot of events, such as a science fair for our school students, in college and have also been in the leading position and have also performed in some.

### **EXPERIENCE**

CareTutors, Flat 3A, House 26, Road Alawul Avenue, Sector 6, Uttara, Dhaka, Dhaka Division, Bangladesh — Teacher

July 2019 - September 2022

- I tutored kids by taking up contracts from them.
- I have had quite experience teaching kids, and I also had some previous experience in teaching.

#### The Educators, Dhanmondi-9/A - Teacher

April 2017 - December 2018

• I finished my O levels and took up a job as a teacher at the coaching center.

### **EDUCATION**

Maple Leaf International School, House # 31 Rd No. 14A, Dhanmondi, Dhaka 1209 - O Levels

June 2016 - January 2017

I gave my O levels from Maple Leaf International School under the British Council examination board and had a GPA of 4.2.

PIE International Education, House # 58 Rd No. 3/A, Sat Mashjid Road, Dhaka — GED

Finished my GED with a GPA of 651.